module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which cast member of Zoom was originally born in Russia?', 
    a: 'Alisa',
    b: 'Jared',
    c: 'Zoe',
    d: 'Lynese',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which part of NYC does Ghostwriter primarily take place?', 
    a: 'Manhattan',
    b: 'Brooklyn',
    c: 'Queens',
    d: 'Staten Island',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'How did Marty from the ABC show Teen Angel die in the pilot?', 
    a: 'Fell off a roller coaster',
    b: 'Ate a 6 month old hamburger',
    c: 'Had a heart attack during a scary movie',
    d: 'Died of boredom during detention',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the primary villain in Rescue Rangers?', 
    a: 'Fat Cat',
    b: 'Flintheart Glomgold',
    c: 'Reginald Bushroot',
    d: 'Banshee',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the Animaniacs parody of the tv show Friends called?', 
    a: 'Best Buddies',
    b: 'Comrades ',
    c: 'Acquaintances',
    d: 'Amigos',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who sang the theme song of Kenan & Kel?', 
    a: 'Coolio',
    b: 'Snoop Dogg',
    c: 'Busta Rhymes',
    d: 'Ice Cube',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'When did the Adventures of Pete & Pete run on Nickelodeon?', 
    a: '1990 - 1992',
    b: '1991 - 1995',
    c: '1995 - 1997',
    d: '1993 - 1996',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Sabrinas longterm boyfriend in Sabrina the Teenage Witch?', 
    a: 'Harvey Kraft',
    b: 'Harvey Kinkle',
    c: 'Harvey Dent',
    d: 'Harvey Keitel',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which famous Star Wars actor voiced The Joker in Batman the Animated Series?', 
    a: 'Harrison Ford',
    b: 'Frank Oz',
    c: 'Ewan McGregor',
    d: 'Mark Hamill',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What object is on Chuckie\'s shirt in Rugrats?', 
    a: 'rocketship',
    b: 'planet',
    c: 'crescent moon',
    d: 'star',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];